I own a design-build ADU company based out of the city of San Diego.
We do $5 million a year, looking to go to 10.
So I'm actually a professional firefighter and have been for the past 18 years.
And so I have yet to go all in on this company because that's what...
Yeah, broke all in.
I'm a servant, I have a servant's heart.
That's what I enjoy doing.
It's a selfish endeavor, right?
So the question is, I make $168,000 a year and I make $600,000 a year in another thing.
And I would like to know when I am secure enough with my $600,000 a year to make up
for $168,000.
It's not about money.
I have more than I could ever have dreamed for, like ever, ever.
You know, you having done that, gone to the other side of it, where are you going to find
meaning?
What do you do on the other side of this thing?
Look for something else to do, right?
So I'm just...
I'm a big believer that a man must have a quest.
This seems much more like a, what do I do with my life question?
Why is there a problem?
The premise of this was, I'm at $168,000, I've got $600,000 a year waiting for me here
and if I actually spend more time on it, I'm sure I could grow it, which I'm sure you
could because you'd have the time back.
But I don't want to quit.
And to me, that's like, then don't quit.
No, I do want to quit.
And to be honest, I was going to ask.
So what are you going to do?
That's a good question.
So you'd like to quit, you're comfortable, you think you can grow this thing more, and
you're afraid to do it.
There you go.
And you rationalize why because of the other reasons, but you know that's not really true.
It's like a therapy session.
So, does that give you the answer?
It does.
Cool.